Shubham Trivedi

+91 9302574024

NIRVANASHUBHAM.07@GMAIL.COM

Career objective

Experience in developing web applications using technologies like Node/Nest Js with Express framework. Has some experience in databases like Mysql & Mongodb. Open to learn new technologies. Motivated to work and excel in the industry.

Skills

Javascript, NodeJS, NextJS, Express, Node, NPM, MySQL, MongoDB, Git, Prisma studio.

Experience

Oct 2022- May 2023

The Metromax Group, Bangalore- Software developer

- Develop gaming applications using NestJS.
- Design and development/enhancement of gaming applications(web & mobile) as per client requirement.
- Analyzing and finalizing the client requirement with respect to the requirement document.
- Build and deployment on test and production server.
- Resolving client issues.
- Attending daily standup/client calls.

Nov 2020 - Sep 2022

Nabha Solutions Ind Pvt. Ltd., Bangalore - Software Developer

- Design and development/enhancement of low latency, high-availability, and performance Web application as per client requirement using JavaScript, NodejS, Express & MongoDB.
- Monitors the transaction health of the applications.
- Worked with ExpressJS to make the API wrappers.
- Writing reusable, testable, and efficient code.
- Resolving client issues which are being reported.

Education

July 2012 - June 2017(B.E.)

Mahakal Institute of Technology, Ujjain, 6.18 CGPA

July 2011- June 2012(12th)

Bhartiya Gyanpeeth, Ujjain, 55%(PCM, State Board)

July 2009- june 2010

Lokmanya Tilak School, Ujjain, 64%(State Board)

Awards

- Participation in Learning sessions.
- Leadership award